医学中心
这是我见过最好的甲床吗
Are these my favorite nail beds I've ever seen?
不是  但它们还算健康
No, but they're fine.
好吧  我其实没打算来这里
Okay. You know, I-- I wasn't actually gonna come here.
但接着我突然想到
But then, I thought, "You know what?
我想散散步
I could-- I could use a walk."
我一直忙于这个
And, um, well, I've just been working on
点对点网络的点子
this peer-to-peer Internet thing,
我散步的时候思路更清晰
and well, I-- I think better when I walk.
如果我一边散步一边思考
If I'm gonna be thinking and walking,
也许我会走到某个特定的地方
I might as well walk somewhere specific.
你上次睡觉是什么时候
Hey, when was the last time you slept?
我不知道
Um... I don't know.
我昨晚本来想睡的
Well, I know I-- I was gonna sleep last night,
我以为我找到了
but, uh... I thought I had this solve